[birds chirping]
[light piano music plays]
[utensils clanking]
[no audible dialogue]
[chair squeaks]
[door opens and closes]
[birds chirping]
[light piano music plays]
[meows]
[exhales]
[wind blowing]
[wind howling]
[indistinct television chatter]
[audience cheers on television]
[thuds]
♪ I hate it when dudes try to chase me ♪
♪ But I love it when you try to save me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just a lady ♪
♪ I love it when we play 1950 ♪
♪ It's so cold that your stare's
'bout to kill me ♪
♪ I'm surprised when you kiss me ♪
♪ So tell me why my gods look like you ♪
♪ And tell me why it's wrong ♪
♪ So I'll wait for you ♪
♪ I'll pray ♪
♪ I will keep on waiting for your love ♪
♪ For you ♪
[volume increases]
♪ I'll wait ♪
♪ I will keep on waiting for your ♪
♪ I hope that you're happy
with me in your life ♪
♪ I hope that you won't
slip away in the night ♪
♪ I hope that you're happy
with me in your life ♪
♪ I hope that you won't slip away ♪
♪ I hate it when dudes try to chase me ♪
♪ I love it when you try to save me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just a lady ♪
[purring]
♪ So tell me why my gods look like you ♪
♪ And tell me why it's wrong ♪
♪ So, so, so, I'll wait ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ I'll pray ♪
♪ I will keep on waiting for your love ♪
♪ For your love, for your love ♪
♪ I will keep on waiting for your ♪
[baby crying]
[uplifting music plays]
[crackling thud]
[camera clicks]
[children chatter]
[uplifting light piano music plays]
[footsteps fade]
[school bell rings]
[lockers clanking]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[children screaming]
[gunshots, screaming]
[sirens blaring]
[phone keypad clicks]
[sirens, screaming continues]
[gunshot echoes]
[rain falling]
[erratic phone alerts]
[deep rumble]
[light piano music plays]
[hopeful piano music plays]
[uplifting keyboard music plays]
♪ In the light of wasted youth ♪
♪ In the fog of finding the truth ♪
♪ When the lights in the sand
keep washing away ♪
♪ With the weight of the words you say ♪
♪ But me, I'm still chasing
what I left behind ♪
♪ After all this time ♪
♪ Mmm-mm ♪
♪ But what did I ask for? ♪
♪ And what did I find? ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ With a love so tightly held ♪
♪ That I wish I hadn't quite felt ♪
♪ And the hard-fought message
not washing away ♪
♪ The weight of the words you say ♪